cstarleague.com 2011-12-21

# Privacy Policy | Collegiate StarLeague

We understand your right to privacy and have prepared this privacy policy to explain how we gather and use any personal information we collect when you use our website. This notice is available as a link from each page of our site. If you have further questions or comments, we invite you to reach out and leave us feedback.

## Information we collect and how it is used

We do not require you to register an account in order to access our website. We do automatically record information that your browser transmits with each request during your visit. The information logged includes your IP address, the date of your visit, your http referrer, browser version, and web request. We use logs to troubleshoot technical problems and to identify malicious users.

Third party analytical tools (such as Google Analytics) that we employ to analyze website usage draw on this same information. These tools use "cookies" to track your use of our website in an anonymous form and transmit this information to third party service providers (such as Google) that evaluate and compile statistical reports on website activity. 

We will not use the analytical tools to track or to collect any personally identifiable information from you and we will not associate any data gathered from this website with any personally identifying information from any source as part of our use of the analytical tools.

We require you to register an account to make use of the full set of website features (such as posting comments or starting threads on our forum). The information we collect during account registration includes:

  * **Username** \- Your username establishes your identity on the website and allows other users to associate you with your content, be it comments or posts.
  * **E-Mail address** \- We will not share your email address with third parties for marketing, spam, or promotional activities. We use your email address when you request to change your password or if we need to send important CSL announcements. Please note that if you become a team coordinator, your email address **displays publicly on your team page**. This feature helps students interested in representing your school in contacting you directly.
  * **Password** \- We hash your password before storing it in our database. We will never log your plain-text password. Please note that account login occurs over a standard http connection so it is not fully safe. **We strongly urge you to use a unique password for your account on the CSL website!**

We require registered users to complete an additional "Player Profile" in order to qualify for participation in the CSL. Information collected for the "Player Profile" includes:

  * **Full Name** \- Your full name **displays publicly** on pages associated with league content (such as player profiles, team profiles, and match reports). Your full name might also appear in news reports, interviews, and website features.
  * You can provide a pseudonym or go by first name only on request, so long as you have a valid school address.
  * **Race** \- Your StarCraft II: Wings of Liberty race **displays publicly** on pages associated with league content.
  * **Character Name and Code** \- Your Battle.net Character Name and Code **display publicly** on pages associated with league content. This information is used to help organize league matches and to query third party sites (such as SC2Ranks.com) for account statistics.

Our full site features include the ability to freely post comments on articles and forum. If you choose to disclose personally identifying information, be aware that CSL is a public web site and anyone is able to read your posts, so there is no expectation of privacy for user-generated content. Where applicable, we will moderate any posts that violate information disclosure laws.

At times, we may provide you with the opportunity to participate in surveys. If you participate, we may request certain personally identifiable information from you. Participation in these surveys or contests is voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes demographic information (such as your major), but could also include contact information (such as your name and email address). We reserve the right to disclose demographical information gathered through surveys publicly or to third parties (such as sponsors), but we pledge to do so anonymously and without disclosing personally identifiable information.

We pledge to never use or share your personally identifiable information in ways unrelated to those described above without informing you of changes to this privacy policy or providing you the ability to opt-in to such use.

## Cookies

This website (and the third party tools it employs) uses cookies (small text files placed on your computer) to store account preferences and to track visitor information in an anonymous form. You may disable cookies from the privacy settings of your browser, but doing so will impair your ability to login using an account as this feature relies on cookies to verify your identity.

## Security

CSL runs on virtualized servers deployed in London at Telecity Group's Powergate facility. These servers are physically secure and our administrators take all reasonable and appropriate measures to secure your personal information digitally from unauthorized access or disclosure.

## How you can access and correct your information

You can access your email address and "Player Profile" through your User Account. Changing your email address requires you to confirm your identity with your password.

## How to contact us

If you have any further questions about our Privacy Policy, we invite you to reach out and leave us feedback. We will try to address your concerns to the best of our ability and to contact you in a timely fashion.

## Updates

We reserve the right to update this Privacy Policy in the future. We will announce any substantial changes, but it is your responsibility to review this notice regularly.
